It has begun!
Ano Channel
Clap!
Crackle, crackle, crackle!
Yes, sir.
Today's guest is this gentleman.
Hi, I'm Soshira. Yes, please.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing here today?
What's so good about it?
You read that.
There are too many cameras.
Oh, there are so many!
So many cameras.
It's a lot for a YouTube channel.
This is not the time for swish.
I'm serious.
I'm sorry, sorry, sorry.
Today's project is...
Let's go horse racing with Sasochan and Ochiru!
Yes!
What?
Let's race with you, Ochuru.
You said you've done horse racing before.
I've never done it in my life.
That's great!
He said he'd be happy to channel me.
Leave it to me.
Horse racing expert.
I'll take care of it.
You're on the losing side.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I know what you're talking about.
I know that.
Some kind of stabbing curse?
I've seen it.
Until last year.
This year it's worse.
Really?
You asked for it.
You'll have fun.
First, I'm going to a shrine.
I'm going to the shrine.
Okay.
You never like shrines.
Neither do you.
A shrine to boost your power?
Let's go there.
There's a place called Okunitama Shrine.
We'll get lucky there.
I'll drive you there.
Can you drive?
I can't.
Do you usually drive?
Not so much.
I saw something on the news.
I saw something on the news about a guy who was driving like an agitator.
He was pissed at the guy who was driving like an agitator.
Which one are you watching?
He was driving like a maniac.
I'm driving so safely that I'm being driven by an aggressive driver.
That's why I'm fine.
What a surprise!
Oh, my God!
No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No!
This program is a variety show where Ana-chan tries various things!
Okay, let's go!
I'll take care of it.
I'll take care of it. You drive.
Hey!
Just a little bit.
It's my first time driving.
I just got my license.
I mean...
It's been a year since I got it.
Almost a year.
Really?
So now is the best time to drive.
Oh, it's the best time.
Right.
Check it out.
That's great.
That's great, right?
Yeah, it's good.
I don't like to drive.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
In a cab or something.
I'll say it like crazy.
Sudden acceleration, sudden stop.
Boom, boom, boom!
Why?
What do you mean?
It's not just for Kinki kids.
Say "boom-boom"!Boom-boom, say it.
What the hell was that?
I'll say it.
Say "boom-boom".
I see.
Here, here, here...
There you go. There you go. There you go.
How's that?
Yeah, it's great.
It's good.
I'm sorry, I'm just the type of guy whose personality changes when I get behind the wheel.
Honestly.
This is the book of turtles.
Oh, no, it's not like that.
Who would go that far?
I'm not like that.
Who wouldn't?
I mean, he was like that before he got in the car.
Who's driving like that behind the wheel?
Aggressive driving?
Normal driving is aggressive driving?
That's right.
That's what I'm talking about.
The words just keep coming.
You're making fun of me.
I'm making fun of you right now.
That's great.
Are you always this out of control when you're driving? All the time.
Yeah, I have.
Oh, my God.
I don't want to sit next to you.
Oh, you know what?
Just drive safe endlessly.
Endlessly?
Endlessly.
That's good.
It's just for today. I'm sleepy.
You're sleepy.
It's early.
ETCOK?
I know you're in there.
What's that? I don't know. ETCOK.
Junior.
No, it's ECC. That's ECC.
Today... clothes... outfits.
P.O.V.
Oh, plain clothes?
That's right.
I choose it myself, all the time.
I always do.
You look cute.
What?
I always thought of you as wearing weird sweatshirts.
Gambling-type stuff.
Oh, yeah, that's the point.
That's what I saw on YouTube.
That's the image I had of you.
That's why there's a boom.
The boom in sweatshirts and hoodies.
You know, the boom in changing clothes.
Yeah.
And there was a time when I was wearing oversized clothes.
Hmm.
Then I got into velour.
Velour?
I only wore velour.
It's so gross.
Is that you?
Ha-ha-ha.
So...
You only wear velours?
I only wear velours.
So it's over.
The boom is over.
And then came the set-up boom.
Yeah.
This is what I bought then.
I only wore set-ups.
Oh, that's over too?
Halfway through.
And now leather.
There's a leather jacket craze.
Leather jacket too?
When I'm in a jacket, I'm pissed off.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You're a pussy.
I'm expressing it with my clothes.
That's right.
Expressionist.
But I'm getting a little tired of all this "kawajan" stuff.
Can't you hurry up?
The boom's over!
Don't you have any suggestions?
You're in that line of work, right?
You know, like making a few coordinated outfits.
No, that's exactly what you do on that channel.
7 Codes Shimamura.
What?Yeah? - Yeah.
About an hour. Seven codes.
I'm glad you liked it.
I made it.
I like fashion.
I like fashion, but I'm a bit of a random person.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, I do.
I'm just going with the flow.
For the day.
Mm-hmm.
What do you think?
You could go back to velour.
No, velour's gonna be tough this time of year, for sure.
Okay? Summer velour?
Summer velour is gross.
Gross?
Gross.
I remember on that channel a long time ago,
I remember when that girl called me "gross" on that channel.
Hahaha.
That was when I first met her.
Oh yeah, that's right. Gross.
What a suguy!
School mizuki.
School Mizuki.
I thought it was gross when he said he liked me too.
It's gross.
It's gross to anyone who hears it.
Do you have a pedophile side to you?
No, I don't.
No?
Who is your favorite actress?
The old Mana Ashida.
You're a pedophile.
What?
That's gross.
What is?
It's scary.
It's from the past. And...
It's not current, is it?
No, that's why.
What?
That's scary.
No, it's because you're not alone with your favorite actress.
I'm a little surprised that it's just the two of us.
It's not the only actress I like, but...
Eo and who?
The old Rimi Ohashi.
Nyandan.
You love kids.
What?
You mean you like him as a woman, right?
No, no, no, no. That's just oligonomics.
No, of course not.
You have to ask me that question.
Like, what actress do you like as a woman?
Who?
The youngest of the Honda sisters.
Oh, my God, I'm scared, I want to run away.
It's okay, it's okay. You're over 20.
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm not kidding.
You have to say you're kidding. It's a joke.
You have to use the word "joke.
What?
Oh, it's getting worse. I'm gonna concentrate on driving.
What? What is it? Bugs?
What's going on out there?
It's so depressing.
Ha-ha-ha.
Bugs?
There's a bug outside.
I'm the bug.
I was threatening it through the window, and now...
And then...
Oh, that's so annoying.
Ha-ha-ha.
No, I can't hear you at home.
Is there a bug in the most important part of your house?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They're out the window?
He was outside the window.
Punch it from the inside.
I punched him from the inside. I think I got through.
Oh, my God.
We're about 400 meters out. We're arriving at our destination.
We're already there!
The drive with the comedian went by so fast.
Driving is a bit of a pain, to be honest.
Yes, it is.
When you said it was just the two of us on the road.
I honestly thought it was crazy.
But it was fun.
Okay, I'll park.
Come on.
We arrived at Okunitama Shrine.We have arrived at Okunitama Shrine.
Wow.
We have to light the fire.
Shrine noisy.
Let's go seriously.
Let's go.
Big door.
Wow, it's big.
Wow, it's amazing. But it's neat.
It's very neat.
I've never been here before. A place like this.
What? This place is amazing.
But you know, it looks like it's been here for a long time.
It's a production.
It's mysterious.
How long has it been here, 1900 years?
150 years?
More than 1900 years?
It was not built in 1900.
The Okunitama Shrine was founded in 111 A.D,
It was founded in the year 111,
111.
Oh, wow.
It is one of the most famous shrines in Tokyo with a history of over 1900 years.
That's amazing.
It's 111.
I'm so happy.
It's an easy chapter.
Then let's go pray.
Ah! That's so sweet.
How to pray.
Here.
Ah! Wow, kind.
Even in English.
Did you know? This.
To be honest, I can't remember it no matter how many times I see it.
Bow twice, clap twice, bow once.
Do it.
Okay. Let's pay our respects.
How much can we put in?
I don't know.
All of it? All the change I have?
Here's some change. All the change I have.
Okay.
Here you go.
That's good.
Pan, pan.
It's the other way around, isn't it?
It's gonna be different.
Total for the two of you?
What, five?
Like this, backwards.
I can't do it today.
Oh, it's the other way around.
So, one drink?
Yes, sir.
May you win the horse race.
Okay.
There's some kind of fortune.
Wanna go check it out?
I spent all my money. I can't do fortunes.
There's also good luck charms.
Good luck charms.
That's nice.
What should I do?
I lent you the money.
Oh, thank you.
Don't buy me a drink.
Give it back.
Buy me a drink.
What do you want?
Your stuff is cute.
It's cute.
What does that have to do with anything?
What about the horse?
Horses?
That's nice.
What do you think?
What about this?
It's a lottery.
I don't want anything bad to happen.
Let's see if today is a win-win situation.
Do you want to take one of each of these?
The prettiest one.
They're all the same.
Because this one's smiling.
Is this the kind you can see?
Which one? I don't care what it is.
I'll take this one.
It's kind of smiling.
Okay, I'll go with this one.
Okay, chi ondol?
Cai ondol.
I've got some coins here.
This one? This one then?
Yeah. - Okay.
I don't know.
Okay.
Okay, that'll be 2,000 yen.Then it's a 2,000 yen piggyback.
Osame
Then give me back 1,000 yen, and so on.
All right.
Please do it for 1,000 yen.
Understood.
Thank you very much.
Let's see the omikujiji.
It's just an ordinary omikuji.
But it says something about what to avoid.
It says what to avoid?
Let's do it.
It's a little interesting
Good luck.
Which way?
I'll go first.
Oh, it's so cute.
I hope I get this one too.
Nice. It's cute.
Come on out, Daikichi.
Here we go.
What's "Suekichi"?
That's funny.
What's "Sueyoshi"?
Sueyoshi is one step above you today.
What's this?
"Be on your guard.
If you let your guard down, there will be trouble.
Proceed with caution.
I see.
Don't let your temperance get the better of you.
Health.
Do not be greedy.
Don't take any chances with the park, the job, the money.
It's easy money. It's all right.
It's all right.
Don't be too optimistic about the amount.
Sueyoshi and
Omonnan.
I'll take it then
Take it off me.
What is it?
Please.
Please, please, please, please.
I hope it's a good one.
I hope it's a big one.
Big luck.
I haven't got it yet.
Wait a minute.
You'll be fine.
Okay, okay, okay.
Here we go.
Okay, back.
It's itchy.
Okay.
What?
It's so tight!
Yeah, it's fine.
Kitchin's good.
You wanted "big luck", didn't you?
I'll tell you.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
Taking a break will give you new ideas.
Your body and mind are important.
You're a busy guy, right, No-chan?
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I work too much.
No rest for the weary.
Don't fly by the seat of your pants! Don't fly by the seat of your pants!
A connection! Don't just be nice
Don't work overtime all the time
Don't just be good at academics!
And so on and so forth
Don't just push yourself too hard
Don't push yourself too hard today
It's not that bad.
That's good. That's good.
I got this, too.
Yeah... and it's even better when you have it.
You know, I bought this for you, and you got the best luck with the book.
I just bought it.
Is that what this is about? Will it take you long?
It takes time.
Until it's affected.
Red? Purple string.
Red is fine.
I don't see red.
Maybe purple would be better.
Purple's fine.
Purple's better.
I don't think of red.
Let's do it the other way around.
Shut up.
Purple's better.
You want red?
You don't remind me of red.He said you don't have the red image.
I'll take you in.
I don't mind, but what's the point?
You don't have the image of red.
So you're going to take care of him because of that image?
You're a couple of thugs on a rocket ship.
Your trash.
You're on my shoe.
Apologize.
Shut up!
You don't have to make a big deal out of every little thing.
I'm just glad it was on the surface.
You got on my shoe.
It's fine.
Don't say that.
I'm such a wreck.
Next time.